<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>AlienFacesExpanded</name>
  <author>Diamonddragon41</author>
  <url></url>
  <targetVersion>1.0.0</targetVersion>
  <description>
    Original mod by Killface
    1.0 Update by InsertKey (thank you!)
    
	 One of the things I found lacking in Alien Faces was that only one hand type was available- human. The main bulk of this mod is adding alien hands 
   and feet to bipedal aliens. I aim to do much more with the mod as it progresses, but I had enough work done I thought some people might like it. 

    Xenn, Orassans, Racc, and Beast Men Tribe Raccoon, Fox, Lynx, Bear and Wolf -- digitigrade paws and claw hand
	  Avian Races, Avail                                                          -- raptor feet and feather wing arm


    If any types of hands and feet are super non-canon to their body parts defs ingame, tell me and I might fix it if it's a bad enough mistake. I kind of used my imagination, lol.

    ----Limitation: hands and feet are bundled together and cannot be mixed and matched-- this is due to how Killiface wrote the code to only look for the handType name,
    even when looking for feet. -------

    To-do List:

    Priority to-dos:
    Beast Men Tribe camel                                                 -- camel hoof and hoof-finger hand
    Beast Men Tribe gazelle                                               -- gazelle hoof and hoof-finger hand
    Beast Men Tribe elephant                                              -- elephant toes and thick finger hand
    Beast Men Tribe pig and elk                                           -- goat hoof and hoof-finger hand
    Equium                                                                -- horse hoof and hoofnhand
    Twi'lek, Android, Zabrak                                              -- human hands and feet (retexture)
    Ni'hal                                                                --if someone can tell me what type of feet they have I can make it!! I have no idea though

    1)Hands and feet for requested races!
      a)bug leg feet and bug leg hands
      b)bug leg feet and mantis hands
      b)reptilian feet
      c)flipper hands 
      d)octopus tentacle arms and feet
      e)any types of hooves I missed lol
      f)crystal/rock hands and feet
      g)ni'hal hands and feet???

    (Need permission from mod owners for these to-dos:) 
      2)Make modified versions of certain Race textures that are eyeless, tailless, earless, so Facial Stuff eyes/tails/ears can be put on them
      3)Make a Tails section of Alien Addon Parts (which killiface left a framework for) and give Xenn, Avali, Racc, Equium Tails seperate from their body so it 
      draws on top of clothes and bounces(copy orassans?)
      4)Make an Ears section of Alien Addon Parts and give Xenn, Racc, Beast Men ears so they draw on top of clothes and bounce (copy orassans?)
      

    To-Try List: (Not guaranteed-- I am a novice programmer! If any coding god wants to help me with this I would be eternally grateful!) 
    1)Make hands have North, South, East sprites like feet do. Currently they ONLY use the south sprite which makes certain hands (especially wings) look goofy,
    especially from the front view. 
    2)Patch the Added Parts system to where peg legs show as wooden pegs-- not as metal feet. 
    3) (unlikely)Make missing fingers actually show up as missing upon the sprites of the hand
    4)Make missing ears actually show up as missing on the sprites of the head when they are addon parts
    5) (unlikely) make feet and hands mix and matchable/ add footType parameter in .xml
    6)Make an ingame config where you can choose the hand n'feet set and other xml options for a race, so you don't have to open the xml and reload to edit them.

    I am open to requests but keep in mind I am super novice coder and might not be able to do it unless it's just .xml stuff or making textures. 
    The request type I am most open to is to add an alien to the mod!!! I want to cover as many aliens as possible.
  </description>
</ModMetaData>